A Guide to the Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Dated files, 1979-1999., Extent: 17.55 cu. ft. (39 boxes) (Box 96-123)
  - Subseries 8. 1999 Legislative Files, Extent: 5.2 cu. ft. (12 boxes)
    - [H.B. 1450] Buena Vista historic preservation (Item 572 #76h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - [H.B. 1450] Center for Assessment and Treatment of Sexually Deviant Disorders (Item 341 #4h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - [H.B. 1450] Commonwealth Competition Council (Item 88#1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - [H.B. 1450] Compensation Board (Item 70 #2h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - [H.B. 1450] Court of Appeals language (Item 28 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - [H.B. 1450] District Courts deputy clerks (Item 30 #2h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - [H.B. 1450] Magistrate positions (Item 33 #2h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - [H.B. 1450] Megan's Law training program (Item 450 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - [H.B. 1450] Mountain View historic preservation (Item 572 #75h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - [H.B. 1450] Offender accountability (Item 455 #4h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - [H.B. 1450] PAPIS (Item 455 #6h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - [H.B. 1450] Roanoke Higher Education Center (Item 260.1 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - [H.B. 1450] Roanoke Higher Education Center (Item 572 #165h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - [H.B. 1450] Roanoke Valley Greenway Commission (Item 94.1 #2h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - [H.B. 1450] Sex offender treatment plan (Item 472 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - [H.B. 1450] Sexual predator community containment (Item 483 #2h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - [H.B. 1450] Sexual predator treatment program (Item 499 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - [H.B. 1450] The Jefferson Center, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - [H.B. 1450] Virginia Council on Juvenile Detention (Item 497 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - [H.B. 1450] Virginia Museum of Transportation (Item 572 #16h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - [H.B. 1450] Virginia Western and Northern Virginia Community Colleges (Item C-18.10 #16h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - [H.B. 1450] Virginia Western Community College (Item C-18.10 #1h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - [H.B. 1450] Virginia's Explore Park (Item 572 #42h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - [H.B. 1450] West Virginia Center for Arts and Science (Item 572 #17h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - [H.B. 1450] Woodrow Wilson birthplace (Item 572 #22h), 1999. (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - [H.B. 1461] Immediate child custody, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 27)
    - [H.B. 1465] Motor vehicle insurance, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 28)
    - [H.B. 1554] Blue Ridge Housing Development Authority, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 29)
    - [H.B. 1556] Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Fund, disposition of benefits, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 30)
    - [H.B. 1557] Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Fund, board of directors, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 31)
    - [H.B. 1558] Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Fund, beneficiaries, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 32)
    - [H.B. 1559] Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Fund, assets of fund, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 33)
    - [H.B. 1583] Removal of action involving more than $3000, 1999. (Box 122, Folder 34)
    - [H.B. 1922] Structured Settlement Protection Act, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
    - [H.B. 2079] Itinerant merchants, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - [H.B. 2250] Branch banks, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - [H.B. 2251] Corporate trusts, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - [H.B. 2252] Regional Training Academy funding, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - [H.B. 2253] Crane operators, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - [H.B. 2759] Census liaison, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - [H.B.] Medical assistance services, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - [H.B.] Travel agency escrow, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - [H.J.R. 838] Celebrating the life of Vivian Ely Herbert, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - [H.J.R. 853] Mill Mountain Theatre, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - [H.J.R] Joint Subcommittee Examining Electric Utility, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - [S.B. 260] Land Management and Stewardship Commission created, 1999. (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Cumulative Chief Patron Report, 1980-1999. (Box 124)
    - Oversize posters, ca. 1980-1999. (Box 125)
    - Video tapes, ca. 1980-1999. (Box 126-129)